Yakantan idoloo
Please let us know if there is any last announcement from Mr. Tohoku.
We, Iginari Tohoku-san, right?
We will be holding a nationwide tour this spring called the National Never Lose Tour.
That's great. The title of the live concert is "The tour that we will never lose.
That's right. With the feeling of never losing,
I would like you to come and see whether or not there will be a performance that you will never lose,
But the time has already started,
If you are able to come after this tour, please check the schedule and come wherever you can.
Where are you going to go in the north and the south, the southernmost part of the country?
Fukuoka.
Who's in Fukuoka?
We are going to a place where there are 12 baseball teams. This time.
I see.
So you're going to Hokkaido, too?
Yes, we are.
That's great.
Spaban and baseball have nothing to do with each other?
I don't think so,
You don't mention it on the tour or something?
I wonder if there will be a baseball element in the tour.
Our manager is a baseball fan,
I think that's why he wants to go to 12 teams,
I see.
I see. Maybe it will come up in the MC.
I see. I don't know at the moment.
I see. I understand for now.
Continue,
And on Friday, December 29th, I will be performing at the Pacifico Yokohama National Hall.
It's huge!
Yes, it is.
It's the biggest venue in our history.
It's the biggest venue in our history,
I'm getting nervous now,
We've been talking about how serious we are this year,
I've always had a serious feeling about it,
This year is even more serious.
This year, we are even more serious.
You are doing the "We can't lose!
That's right. That's part of it,
This year, we are determined to go for it, and we are working hard,
I hope you will come to the Pacifico at the end of the year.
Please come to the Pacifico at the end of the year.
I am looking forward to it.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
From Mr. Yasha.
Tea will be served from me.
Thank you very much.
By the way, my face-maker made it for me.
Is this it?
Yes.
He drew my face so precisely.
What? It's cute.
I had a difference of opinion with the captain about this one, too,
There are two faces.
What? What do you mean?
The captain thinks this one is the better one.
I said, "This one is definitely the better one.
Then, he asked me to draw both of them.
It's a two-sided face.
It's true. I could only see this one.
I didn't want to compromise on that.
So this is the end of the battle between Kaja and the captain.
Yes, it was.
It's a common fight.
Is it a common fight?
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
I see.
Then today's tea is for you.
It's a blend of herbal teas for the throat.
Wow, how stylish. Thank you very much.
Well, I hope you will drink it for me.
Bon appétit.
Wow! Delicious!
That's a good reaction.
It is very delicious.
Various locales look delicious, too.
See you later. See you soon. Among the many stories I've heard,
I'm sorry to end on this note,
I don't mean it's painful, but it can't be helped that you're cute.
I just want to say something cute.
I hope you have gotten to know me, Yuna Hasaki, a little better this time,
I still have a lot of charms to share with you,
I would be very happy if you all could get to know me.
So, thank you very much for your time today.
This program is led by Haghtan's favorites, Mr. Murato, Mr. Kuro, and Ms. Yumi,
Hiroshi Yamamoto, and Shige-san from Nagano, who would like to drink draft beer.
Thanks everyone!